[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Director of movies such as The Color Purple (1985), The Sugarland Express (1974) and Escape to Nowhere (1961).", "correct_answer": "Steven Spielberg", "incorrect_answers": ["Quentin Tarantino", "Sergio Leone", "Frank Zappa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which quasar is the brightest as seen from Earth?", "correct_answer": "3C 273", "incorrect_answers": ["PSR0031-07", "PKS0405-123", "OQ 172"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To what continent are raccoons native?", "correct_answer": "North America", "incorrect_answers": ["South America", "Australia", "Both Americas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is chemophobia?", "correct_answer": "fear of chemicals", "incorrect_answers": ["fear of trees", "fear of amphibians", "fear of angina or choking"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what movie did Lt Kaffee ask Col. Jessep, Did you order the Code Red? DID YOU ORDER THE CODE RED!", "correct_answer": "A Few Good Men", "incorrect_answers": ["Twelve Angry Men", "JFK", "Witness for the Prosecution"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Orange River is the longest river in which country?", "correct_answer": "Republic of South Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Canada", "Chile", "Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of effect of these is the main reason for the existence of the water cycle on Earth?", "correct_answer": "The Sun", "incorrect_answers": ["Thermal energy in the Earths core", "Gravitational forces", "The Moon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie was the following tag line used to promote: Up is down, black is white, and nothing is what it seems?", "correct_answer": "Millers Crossing", "incorrect_answers": ["Barton Fink", "Raising Arizona", "L.A Confidential"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During the movie Fast Times at Ridgemont High, Brad works at 2 different places.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Acrophobia is the fear of flying.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest extant butterfly species on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Queen Alexandras Birdwing", "incorrect_answers": ["Rajah Brookes Birdwing", "Goliath Birdwing", "Cairns Birdwing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1966 movie The Good, the Bad and the Ugly, the gold is buried in an unmarked grave next to the grave of Arch Stanton.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]